（古市）
＜皆さん　いかがお過ごしですか？古市です。→
Everyone, I hope you are all well.
This is Furuichi.
ようやく夏休みに入り
あの不良学校からも解放され→
Summer vacation is finally here, and I have
been released from that school full of delinquents.
オレは今　家族と
南の島に来ています。→
Currently, I have come to this
tropical island with my family.
え？男鹿はどうしたって？→
Where's Oga, you ask?
あっははは…知るか。
皆さんもそろそろ→
Don't know, don't care.
I'm sure you can do without all the
pointless fights among delinquents, yes?
あの不良たちのアホアホ
勢力争いに　あきた頃でしょ？→
いや～オレはもう
正直うんざりですよ＞
Honestly, I had just about enough of it...
（ほのか）
≪ねえ　お兄ちゃ～ん。この人達も
東京から来たんだって≫
Hey, Bro! These girls said
they also came from Tokyo!
（古市）
ははは…友達が見つかって
良かったじゃないか。→
I'm glad you've made some new friends.
子供は子供どう…。
Kids should play toge...
（古市）＜てなわけで今回は
予定を変更して→
And so, this episode, we'll
change things up a bit.
古市貴之１５歳・夏。
「アバンチュールな恋の予感です」→
Furuichi Takayuki, 15 years old...
Summer.
An Adventurous Premonition of Romance...
…をお送りしたいと＞
おっ！？
Presented by myself, Furu...
（アランドロン）ん～。
お…。
ん～。
This...
お　お…。
This big old guy
（アランドロン）あぁ～～！！
うわぁ～！
う～ん　パカッ！
（古市）あああっ！
（古市）＜前略　お袋さま＞
Dear Mom...
うわ～ぁ！！
うわ～うぐっ。
（男鹿）お　来た来た。
うっ…。
Oh, look who's here!
市民プール　行こうぜ。
（ベル坊）ダッ！
Let's head to the public pool!
（古市）＜友達って…何ですか？＞
Who needs friends, anyway?
（アランドロン）
＜これは　ひょんなことから
赤ん坊を育てることになった→
This is a story of a high school
juvenile delinquent who,
不良高校生の物語。ただし　その
赤ん坊は普通の赤ん坊ではなく→
through some strange circumstances,
is raising a baby.
But this baby is no ordinary baby...
魔王の子だったのです＞
It is a baby Demon Lord!
You're Not a Bad Specimen of a Man
（古市）すげ～人だな。→
That's quite a crowd.
なあ　男鹿　あらためて聞くが
これは何の拷問だ？
Let me ask you again, Oga...
What kind of torture is this?
何って～
夏といえばプールだろ？
ダ～ブ！
What? Summer means going
to the pool, you know?
まあ確かに…だがな高級リゾートの
プールサイドにいたオレがだ→
Yeah, I'll agree to that.
But I was poolside at a fancy resort.
何でこんな　すし詰め状態の
ムシ風呂みたいな市民プールに→
I was asking why I have to be crammed in like
a can of sardines into this bug-infested pool?
いなければならんのかと
聞いてるんだ！
ん？なんかムカつくから。
Huh?
'Cause it kinda pissed me off.
直球だな　おいっ。つ～うか
それ　お前も楽しくね～だろ！？
Throwing straight balls at me, huh?
And wait, do you enjoy this?
あぁ～オレはだってほら→
Well, you know...
お前のガッカリした顔が
見れたら　それで満足だから。
As long as I can see your
dejected face, I'm all good.
《えっ　何　言ってんのこいつ！》
What the hell is he saying?!
いや～お前んちに行ったら
誰も出ね～しさ。
I went to your house, but
there wasn't anyone there.
((ふ～るいちく～ん　あ～そ～ぼ))
((ダ～～！))
Furuichi-kun! Let's go out and play!
((おっさん　何してんだ？))
Whatcha doin', big fellow?
You see, Furuichi-dono and his family
have all gone on vacation to a resort.
（アランドロン）((それが…古市殿は→
家族そろって南の島にバカンスへ
お出かけになられてしまい→
私は置いてきぼりを
くらったので→
And they have left me behind.
こうして　古市殿のお帰りを
お待ちしている次第です))
I am now sitting here waiting
for Furuichi-dono to return.
((ダー　アイヤ！))
((そうだな。これはいわゆる→
See, this is why they call this
a class-based society, Baby Beel.
格差社会っていうヤツだな
ベル坊))
あ…。
まっ　おっさんも可哀想だし→
Well, the big guy seemed lonely, and
I couldn't let you hog all the fun,
お前だけ　いい目を
見させるのはイカンと。
そこで　おっさんにひと働き
してもらったってわけだ。
ダブーッ。
so I had him do a little job for me.
え～っと　それ…。
Um... And you never considered coming
to the resort yourself instead?
逆にお前も　リゾートに来るという
発想にはならなかったの？
ハッハハハ！何　言ってんだ。
そんなことして…あっ！
What are you talking about?
That's just...
ア～ッ！
あああ～～っ！
ア～～ッ！
もうどっか行けよ！
Just go somewhere and die...
はあ～何が悲しくて男２人と
赤ん坊で市民プールに…。
How sad is it for two guys to
take a baby to a public pool...
せめて　ヒルダさんがいれば…。
If Hilda-san was here at least...
あ！？
（千秋）あ？
あっ！
Chiaki, we got a table over here!
（寧々）≪千秋　席こっちだから≫
（由加）ちょうど空いてたっス。
One just opened up!
おおお…。
Your're... Oga's lackey.
（寧々）あんた…男鹿の連れの。
《神様って　いるんだね》
God really exists, you know?
いや～偶然ですね～。
（由加）そうっスね～。
Wow! What a coincidence!
Yeah...
まあ～ね。
Sure...
《てゆ～か
何で一緒に座ってんの？》
And why is he sitting with us?
で　皆さん　お揃いのようですけど
邦枝先輩は？
It looks like you're all here,
but where's Kunieda-senpai?
（由加）葵姐さんは夏休み入ってから
ず～っと修業中っス。
Madame Aoi's been training ever
since summer vacation started.
修業！？ま　まさか花嫁修業ですか？
Training?
Could she be... A bride-in-training?!
このままじゃダメだって
一から鍛え直すつもりらしいよ。
She said she wasn't good enough as she was
now, and wanted to start over from square-one.
っていうか　あんた　めんどくさい
リアクションするわね。
And man, your reactions are just annoying.
はぁ～そうですか～。
I see...
石矢魔の女王の水着姿も
見たかったのに…。
I wish I could have seen
Ishiyama's Queen in a swimsuit.
あぁぁ…。
《ストレートな奴》
This bastard doesn't beat around the bush.
（涼子）ただ修業ばっかりだと
気が滅入ると思って。
I thought that just training all
the time would be depressing...
本当は無理やり
連れ出したんスけどね～。
We had to force her to come.
じゃあ　やっぱり来てるんですね！
Then, she is here?
ど　どこですか！？
W-Where is she?
あぁぁ…。
《本当にストレートな奴》
He sees a bush, he heads straight for it...
いやぁ　さっきまで
一緒だったんスけどね～。
Well, we were together before.
（寧々）それよりあんたの方こそ
男鹿と一緒じゃないの？
Anyway, weren't you with Oga?
ああ　ショック受けて
その辺で呆けてますよ。
Yeah.
He took a shock, he's spaced
out around here somewhere.
あ　ははは…南。南の島。
ダ～ブ～。
Tropical...
Tropical island...
ようこそ。それそれ。めんそ～れ。
ダ～ブ～。
Welcome!
Ha-ha... Aloha...
（邦枝）
《どうしよう…まさかこんな所で
アイツと出くわすなんて》
What'll I do?
I never thought he'd show
up in a place like this!
《この水着おかしくないかな？
中学の時のなんだけど…》
Isn't this swimsuit a little weird?
It's my swimsuit from middle school...
《ちょっと地味すぎるかも…》
Maybe it's too plain!
フーン。
あっ　呼んできましょうか？
（寧々）その必要はないわ。
So should I call him over?
There's no need for that.
姐さんが　レッドテイルをやめる
キッカケになった相手に→
I'd rather not see the guy who caused
Madame Aoi to quit the Red Tails.
好きこのんで会いたくないから。
うん。
寧々さん…。
こえ～っス。
Nene-san...
Scary...
そうですか…。
I see.
それはおいといて　じゃ男鹿抜きで
楽しくお喋りしましょうか。
Well, so be it.
Let's have fun chatting
then, no Ogas allowed!
人の話　聞いてる！？
Are you even listening to me?
あ　アイスキャンディーとか
食いたくないスか？
Sure.
Would you like some ice-cream pops?
ほら　あそこにちょうど
売ってるし。
There's a guy over there selling some.
（高島）≪お　古市じねえか？≫
あん？
Oh, if it isn't Furuichi?
（高島）久しぶりだな。ええ？
It's been a while, hasn't it?
《げっ　こいつら中学の時の…》
Those are guys from my middle school days...
相変わらず　女連れか。
オレらにも紹介しろよ。
Still chasing the girls, are you?
Introduce us, will ya?
（不良達）ヒヒヒ…。
Four of us, and four of you. Perfect!
４対４で　丁度いいじゃねえか。
エッへへ…
ただし　お前抜きでな。
知り合い？
Well, not including you!
Friends of yours?
あっ　いや　中学の時の先輩で
高島さんって…。
Well, he was an upperclassman
in my middle school...
Name is Takashima-san.
おいおい　何だそりゃあ？
Hey, what's with that?
もっとあんだろう？
好感度の上がる紹介が。
You can introduce me a little
better than that, don't you think?
お世話になってますとかよ～。
Like thanking me for the favor I did you...
ヒヒヒ…気をつけた方がいいよ。
こいつ根っからの女たらしだから。
You better watch out.
This guy's a womanizer to the core!
そうそう。君たちのこと
エロい目でしか見てね～から。
Yeah! He looks at you and
only thinks about sex!
え～っと
こいつら何なんスかね？
Um... What's with these guys?
超キモイんですけど。
They are really creeping me out.
ん…。
無視しな　小物だよ。
Ignore them, they're small-time.
え！？
ヤバイよヤバイよ！エロ野郎の古市君に
目つけられちゃ大変だぁ。
Uh-oh, uh-oh!
You're in trouble when pervy
Furuichi-kun's got his eyes on you!
（高島）まっ　安心していいぜ。→
Well, don't you worry.
こいつ　オレたちには
頭あがんね～からさ。→
He won't go against us.
それよりも　オレたちと
健全に遊んだ方が楽しいぜ。
Playing around with us is
much more wholesome and fun.
あんたたち！
（バシャッ）
Look here, you guys...
クッ…。
（高島）
（邦枝）
す　すいません。水着くださ～い！
Excuse! I need a swimsuit!
（店員）≪は～い　どのような
水着でしょうか？≫
Yes? What kind of swimsuit?
（邦枝）≪な　何でもいいから
かわいいのを！≫
Whatever! A cute one!
（邦枝）《これなら　きっと！》
With this, I'm sure...
フフフッ…ヘヘヘッ…。
ベル坊　もうアレだな。
Baby Beel, you know what?
オレ達の夏は終わったのかもな。
ダ？
Our summer is over, yeah...
ダ！？ダ～ブ！イイッ～！
Baby Beel, I ain't doin' anything today.
ベル坊　今日はなんもしねえぞ。
もう寝る…。
Gonna take a nap.
ファ～。
ダ～ブ！
ダ！ダ！ダブッ！
ダ～ブダ！アイ～！！
ダ～ブダ！アイ！ダ！ダ～ダ！
アダダッ！ダブダブダ…！！
ダ～ブ！ダブダブダブダブ…！
ダ～！キ～キッ！ダッ！！キ～！
ダ～～ブッ！
あ？
ダ～ブ！キャッキャッ…！
アハハハ…。
ダーブ　ダー！
ダッダー！！
アハハハ…。
めんそ～れ　南の島にめんそ～れ。
ダッ　ダーダブ　ダッ！
Aloha...
Aloha on a tropical island...
ようこそ～
南の島へ　めんそ～れ。
Welcome to a tropical island... Aloha...
You bastard...
てめえ　何のマネだ。
What are you trying, huh?
It's like an oven here, Senpai.
いやあ　熱いっすね　先輩。
頭　冷えました？
Did I cool your hot head?
Furuichi, you bastard!
古市　てめえ　コラァ！
You wanna get the crap beat out of you?
ボコボコにされてえのかぁ？
Wait.
（高島）≪待て≫
高島さん！
Takashima-san!
You haven't changed, Furuichi.
変わってねえなあ　古市。→
You still act all cool in front of girls.
女の前で　すぐそうやって
カッコつけるクセ。
Don't tell me you forgot about the
time that got you in deep shit, right?
てめえ　それで
痛い目に遭ったこと→
まさか忘れたわけじゃ
ねえだろうなあ！
フフフ…傑作だったよなあ。
あの時の　お前。
What a piece of work I
did on you back then...
（高島）
((ヘッ　みっともねえなあ。→
You're pathetic.
This is what happens when you
act all tough in front of girls.
女の前でカッコつけるから
そうなるんだぜ))
((わかったら　土下座して詫びろ))
If you get it, then grovel
and beg forgiveness.
((クッ…))
（高島）
((聞こえなかったのか？
土下座だっつってんだよ))
Did you hear me? I said grovel!
フフフ…ウッ！ハハハ！
ワハハハ！
やめろって！おい！！→
Stop it, you...
ハハハ…ハハハ！
（ドスッ！）
うっ！
（高島）ぐおおおっ！
Why, you...
てめえ！高島さんに
なんてことしやがる！
What have you done to Takashima-san?
You got nerve for a weakling!
弱いくせにイキリやがって。
てめえなんぞ
いつでもボコれんだぞ！
We could beat you any time we wanted!
Yeah, no kidding...
（古市）そうっすね～。
Ow!
《いってえ　頭突き痛てえよ
これ…》
Dang, headbutting hurts...
As you say, I'm seriously weak, so...
おっしゃる通り
俺　マジ弱いっすから。
I'll run.
逃げます。
アデュー！
Adieu!
Damn him...
ちきしょう…追え！
絶対に逃がすんじゃねえ！
After him! Don't let him get away!
R-Right!
は　はい！
待て　コラー！
Wait for us!
な　何か大変なことに
なっちゃったスね。
This has gotten kind of serious.
That Furuichi guy should
have just let it go...
あの古市って子も
やめとけばいいのに。
Oh?
あら…なかなか男じゃない。
Not a bad specimen of a man...
（千秋）焼きそば…。
Yakisoba...
≪そっちいたか？≫
≪ダメだ　潜ってる！≫
Is he over there?
He's underwater!
Damn it! There's even more people!
クソッ！ますます人が
増えてきやがった。
I can't find him like this!
これじゃ捜せねえぞ！
That little shit thinks he
can get the better of me?
クソが…なめやがって　あの野郎。
絶対見つけて　ボコってやる！
I'll find him and beat him good!
Hey, it's me.
おう　俺だ！今すぐ手空きのもん
集めて　市民プールに来い。
Bring everyone who's free
to the public pool now.
No, not for picking up chicks!
ああ？ナンパじゃねえ！
エロ野郎を叩きのめすんだ！
We're gonna beat the crap out of a pervert!
Next...
お次は…。→
Hey, lifeguard!
おい　監視員！
（監視員）ん　何か？
What is it?
友達が　ずっとプールから
上がってこねえんだ。
A friend of mine hasn't come out
from under the water for a while.
He might be drowning!
もしかしたら溺れてるかも
しれねえ。助けてくれや。
Please, save him!
What?!
何っ！
（ピーッ！）
Fools... They'll never find
me in this crowd of people.
《バーカ！この人ごみの中で
そうそう見つかるかってえの。→
Keep on searching all you want.
一生捜してろ！→
Next, I just need to find
Oga, then beat it outta here.
あとは男鹿を見つけて
さっさとズラかれば…ああっ？→
あれ？》
Huh?
Where'd everyone go?
（古市）誰もいない。
I found a Furuichi-kun!
（高島）古市君　見～っけ！
Didn't you have a friend that was drowning?
（監視員）
君達！
溺れた友達がいるんじゃ…。
Now, now... Just be quiet and watch!
まあまあ　黙って見てな。
Furuichi, resign yourself.
古市　観念しな。
もう逃げ場はねえよ。
You ain't got nowhere left to run.
《いつの間にか増えてるし…》
All of a sudden there's a lot more of 'em.
You've been taking trash to the
head of West High, Takashima-san!
（不良）
≪てめえは　西高のヘッドの
高島さんに上等ブッこいたんだ≫
You better be prepared to
accept the consequences.
（不良）≪それ相応の覚悟は
してもらわねえとな≫
Don't think you can escape!
（不良）≪逃げられると思うなよ≫
あ～あ　ヤバイ展開ですね。
どうするっスか　これ。
Things have gotten dangerous.
What should we do?
Just watch.
ま　見ときな。
でも　ウチらにも　少しは関係が…。
But we're also kinda involved...
おいしい。
Yummy...
それ～！
≪ヤッホー！≫
おいおい　ヤベエよ　これ。
どうすりゃいいんだ…あっ！
This is bad... What'll I do?
ダブー。
男鹿！
Oga?!
All right!
よっしゃ！お前がいれば
なんとかなる！やっておしまい！
With you here, we'll manage somehow!
Go get 'em!
あれ？
ダァ？
ごめん　それは…めんそ～れ…。
Ha, no... Aloha...
Tropical island... Aloha...
南の島に　めんそ～れ
あ～　それそれ。
Ha, ha-ha...
Get yourself together, Oga!
しっかりしろ！男鹿！
A gang with boards and
bats are coming to get us!
廃材とか　バット持った連中に
囲まれてるんだぞ！
キーッ！
A board in each hand, all aboard!
廃材片手に　ハイサイサーイ
おじさんハイサイ　めんそ～れ。
Big guy, all aboard to aloha!
（高島）フフフ…頼みの綱の男鹿も
使い物にならねえようだな。
Looks like you can't rely
on Oga like you always do!
It's over, Furuichi.
終わりだ　古市。
Or maybe you'll grovel down in the pool!
それじゃあ今度は　ここで
土下座してもらおうか。１０分位な。
For about, 10 minutes, say?!
出た　高島さんのムチャ振り。
≪そりゃ見ものだわ≫
マジ　ウケる。
There it is! Takashima-san
is seriously twisted.
I can't wait to see it!
What a show, baby!
すいません…。
Sorry...
Huh?
ああ？今さら詫（わ）びか？
（古市）これだけは　やりたく
なかったんですけど…。
You gonna apologize, now?
I didn't want to have to do this...
What's that supposed to mean?
何だそりゃ？ハハハ！
Are you an idiot?
≪バッカじゃねえの？≫
≪この期に及んで　ハッタリかよ≫
You trying to bluff? Now?!
What a show, baby!
≪マジ　ウケる！≫
いえ　ひどく卑怯（ひきょう）な
方法なんで　本当にすいません。
No, it's just... I'm sorry about
using this really underhanded move.
ダダダ…？
ええ？おい！
頼むぜ　ベル坊…泣いてくれ！
I'm counting on you, Baby Beel... Cry for me!
ダダダ…！
ビィ～ヤ～ッ！！
（古市）
わ～ははは～！超必殺技！
古市ローリングサンダーブラスト！
Super Special Move!
Furuichi Rolling Thunder Blast!
What just happened?
何が起こったんスかね。
（古市）ナーハハハハッ！
Furuichi-kun... A word?
古市君　ちょっと…。
ダブー…。
Oh, you're awake?
あ　起きた？アハハハ…。
Furuichi, you idiot!
古市　バカ！
（古市）やっぱね！
I knew it!
（千秋）あっ！
（寧々）葵姐さん！
（邦枝）あっ！
Madame Aoi!
何やってたんすか？
捜したんですよ。
What have you been doing?
We were looking for you.
Oh, well...
えっと　その…あ！そういえば
アイツ来てるんだって？
Anyway, I heard that he's here?
アイツ？
ああ　男鹿ですか？
He?
Yeah. Oga.
えっ！？お　男鹿なんて
ひと言も言ってないけど。
Oga? I never said anything about Oga...
さっき監視員に　古市と一緒に
つまみ出されましたよ。
He and Furuichi were kicked out
by the lifeguard a moment ago.
えっ？ああ…。
（寧々）葵姐さん　その水着…。
Madame Aoi... That swimsuit...
えっ？あっ…。
No!
い　いやあ！み…見ないで！
D-Don't look!
だって　可愛いのくださいって
言ったら　こんなのしか…。
I said I wanted something
cute, and this was all they...
キュート！
Cute!
（高島）
クソッ！古市のヤツ！まだ
そう遠くへは行ってねえはずだ！
Damn that Furuichi!
He can't have gotten far!
Takashima-san...
高島さん…。
もう止めときませんか。
Maybe we should just give up?
Shut up!
うるせえ！
さんざんコケにされたんだぞ！
We were all burnt pretty good, right?
Ice-cream pops! Get your ice-cream pops!
You just wanna let him go?
このまま引っ込めるか！え～冷たいアイスキャンディーは
いかがですか～。
冷たくて甘～い
アイスキャンディー。
Hey, you!
おい　そこの！さっき　この辺を
スカしたストレートヘアと→
Did a brat with straight hair
and a guy with an evil look
裸の赤ん坊を背負った目つきの
悪いヤツが通らなかったか？
and a naked baby on his back pass by here?
Ice-cream pop? Here you go.
アイスキャンディーですか。
まいど。
Did you hear me? Hey!
聞いてなかったのかよ！
おいっ！
It doesn't look like you're going to
purchase some of my precious wares.
俺の大事な売り物を
受け取ってくれねえみてえだな。
お　お前は～っ！！
You're...
（東条）
え～　冷たいアイスキャンディーはいかがっすか？
Ice-cream pops! How about
some frozen ice-cream pops?
Frozen and sweet ice-cream pops!
冷たくて甘～い
アイスキャンディー。
This time, it's my stomach...
今度は腹が…。
見事に焼け残ったな。
That's quite a tan-line you got.
ダーッ！
あっ！→
ヒルダさ～ん！
（ヒルダ）ん？
Hilda-san!
お前たち　もう帰るのか？
You're coming back already?
Yeah. Thanks to a certain
someone, we got kicked out...
ああ。どこかの誰かさんのせいで
いられなくなっちまったからな。
あっ　ああ…。
I see.
そうか。せっかく魔界から
取り寄せた水着を持ってきたのに→
And after I went all the way to the
Demon World to bring back a swimsuit...
Too bad.
残念だ。
み　水着！？
Swimsuit?
《はっ！いや　待て…
前にも　こんな事が…》
Wait, this happened before.
アハハハ！わかってますよ
ベル坊のですよね？
Oh, I know... For Baby Beel, right?
What are you talking about?
何を言っている。
ちゃんと大人用だぞ。
This one is for adults only.
What?!
な　何ぃ！
わかりました　ヒルダさん！
I understand, Hilda-san!
Then let's go to another pool straight away!
それなら今から　別のプールへ
行きましょう！ねっねっ！
Okay, okay?!
グフフ…。
I will not let you!
させるか～！！
は～！！は　は～っ！
What do you, ah, think?
いかがですかな？
あ～ん。
（古市）似合ってるから　帰って…。
It looks good on you, so go away, 'kay?
The Great Demon Lord has sent a
wonderful present to the Master.
Now accept it gladly.
What's this?
A Demon morning-glory seed, Demon insect
collecting kit, and seething notebook?
It's summer homework.
Baby Beel, you're excited about this?
On the next Beelzebub: How About
Some Demon World Homework?
By the way, Demon World radio
exercises go from 1 to 362509048.
Will you do them?
Hell, no.